-Fix anomaly bleeding that did not cause blood loss
-Reagent A no longer loses its potency over time
-The negative impact of Reagent A now cannot be permanently cured with stabilocin
-The bracelet can be carried in the inventory and is equipped in the gene splicer slot instead of the bag slot
-Hooded Man now has a backpack and more fashionable outfit
-EW-P6 now requires a spike instead of a spark gap to craft.
-ED-P2.5 now requires wax instead of a spike to craft
-The spike and spark gap again interact with each other. I hope they will not cause the death of the server.
-Added a new item - a pirate shield, can be found on pirate submarines
-ED-P7 is now 10% more efficient than a screwdriver and wrench, 15% more efficient than conventional welding, requires fuel to operate and consumes 10-15% more fuel.
-Added new alien trinkets, 5
-Added new "things", 2
-"Thing" can now spawn in abandoned labs in ruins
-New rooms in ruins, various minor fixes of old ones
-Added Improved Tool Belt purchasable from Engineer and City Traders



  <entitydescription.artmod_alientrinket6_hugebracelet>在异星遗迹中发现的小型造物。对有所了解的人来说，它看起来像是地球上的首饰——手镯？对于其他人来说它只是一件形状怪异的造物罢了。你可以用基因拼接器槽位佩戴这玩意...但这真的值得吗？</entitydescription.artmod_alientrinket6_hugebracelet>
  
  <entityname.artmod_alientrinket12_animation>Alien Curio</entityname.artmod_alientrinket12_animation>
  <entitydescription.artmod_alientrinket12_animation>Minor artifact found in alien ruins.
Suspiciously resembles one of the previously seen trinkets, only smaller and constantly in motion. And it seems to defy the laws of gravity.</entitydescription.artmod_alientrinket12_animation>
  <entityname.artmod_alientrinket13_nomnom>Alien Box</entityname.artmod_alientrinket13_nomnom>
  <entitydescription.artmod_alientrinket13_nomnom>Minor artifact found in alien ruins.
Irregular shaped box with a hole in the center. Looks like you can put something in there. But it's hardly necessary.</entitydescription.artmod_alientrinket13_nomnom>
  <entityname.artmod_alientrinket14_whereisit>Alien Cross</entityname.artmod_alientrinket14_whereisit>
  <entitydescription.artmod_alientrinket14_whereisit>Minor artifact found in alien ruins.
Buzzing with energy. An extremely rare and valuable find, but even less often it ends up in research centers.</entitydescription.artmod_alientrinket14_whereisit>
  <entityname.artmod_alientrinket15_mimic>Thing</entityname.artmod_alientrinket15_mimic>
  <entitydescription.artmod_alientrinket15_mimic>Causes a persistent feeling that this is not what it seems.</entitydescription.artmod_alientrinket15_mimic>
  <entityname.artmod_alientrinket16_invisible>Something</entityname.artmod_alientrinket16_invisible>
  <entitydescription.artmod_alientrinket16_invisible>Here is something you can feel and hold in your hands.</entitydescription.artmod_alientrinket16_invisible>